Number of Language	3	For Customer Reference Only!
Enum Value	Module Name	Region ID	Description	English	Tr_Chinese	Si_Chinese	
DO NOT MODIFY	DO NOT MODIFY	DO NOT MODIFY	DO NOT MODIFY	*#0044#	*#0886#	*#0086#	
STR_ID_SAFE_MODE_EXIT	SafeMode	TEXT	Exit Safe Mode	Exit safe mode	退出安全模式	退出安全模式	
STR_ID_SAFE_MODE_HELP_TEXT	SafeMode	TEXT	Help text	Your phone is in safe mode now. This might be caused by a recent software installation, upgrade, or removal. All download contents have been disabled now. Restart the phone to exit safe mode, or do it later manually. Restart now ?	你的手機目前正在安全模式下運行，所有下載內容將無法使用。軟體的安裝、升級或卸載都有可能導致手機進入此模式。重新開機可以退出安全模式，或者稍後手動重啟。重新開機嗎？	您的手机目前正在安全模式下运行，所有下载内容将无法适用。软件的安装、升级或卸载都有可能导致手机进入该模式。重启手机可以退出安全模式，或者稍后手动重启。重启手机吗？	
STR_ID_SAFE_MODE_RESTART	SafeMode	TEXT	Restart	Restart now	重新開機	重启手机	
STR_ID_SAFE_MODE_QUERY_CHECK	SafeMode	TEXT	Do you want to launch autostart app one by one ?	Do you want to launch autostart app one by one ?	確認要開始啟動應用程式嗎？	确认要开始启动应用程序吗？	
STR_ID_SAFE_MODE_QUERY_LAUNCH	SafeMode	TEXT	Query if launch the app	Do you launch the application :	啟動應用程式：	启动应用程序：	
STR_ID_VAPP_MODE_DO_IT_LATER	SafeMode	TEXT	Do it later	Do it later	稍後再重啟	稍后再重启	
##number	6
